

Kenny Deschuyteneer **Web Developer**

About me

Hi! I'm a young enthusiastic developer who likes making shiny stuff on the internet. I've got a healthy dose of motivation, a decent couple of years of experience and a nice portfolio to show for it.

Besides the necessary skills for web developing, there are a few things that tickle my fancy, such as data visualisation, animations, logo design, game design, video editing, ...

I've enjoyed a broad education in computer science, which translates in my career to swiftly picking up new technologies, frameworks, and the likes.

Overall, my aim is to enrich the world with digital content that works well, is accessible, and looks good.

Skills

React, Vue.js, Web Components | JS (Vanilla, ES6 and beyond), TS | HTML | CSS | Back-end development (TS/JS) | AEM, Gatsby, Contentstack | AWS AppSync & Lambda | GIT, CI-CD, Jira, Microsoft TFS

Contact

+32 476 20 88 75

kenny.deschuyteneer@gmail.com

in /in/deschuytemeneer

/deschuytemeneer

Education

2012 - 2014 Master of Science: Computer Science | VUB, Belgium

2009 – 2012 Bachelor in Computer Science | VUB, Belgium

2014 - 2016 Graphics & Digital Media (not finished) | Arteveldehogeschool, Gent

Experience

01/2023 - 12/2023 travelling through Australia

I had the opportunity to move to Australia for a year (under a working holiday visa). I did not completely shy away from programming, though: I built my own portfolio website (vanilla HTML/CSS), and one for a friend (Gatsby).

09/2022 - 01/2023 at JnJ as Frontend Developer for TEMPO (as IT Consultant Capgemini)

Senior developer. Developing components and pages for Gatsby, using modern Redux to connect to a REST API.

05/2021 – 08/2022 at JnJ as Full-stack Developer for SA Xpress (as IT Consultant Capgemini)

Senior developer and designer. Full Typescript stack with a modern React frontend (+ Material UI) and a GraphQL backend using AWS AppSync, Lambda and APIGateway. Was lead dev for the last half year of the project (3-4 people).

10/2019 - 04/2021 at VRT as Front-end Developer for the VRT NU team (as IT Consultant Capgemini)

Junior developer. Web components (ES6 and SCSS). Contributed to the VRT NU design system (web components using StencilJS and Storybook).

03/2017 - 09/2019 at ENGIE Electrabel as Front-end Developer (as IT Consultant Capgemini)

Junior developer. Implemented multiple front-end SPA's in VueJS, helped restructure CSS of the website using SCSS/SASS.